Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/dileep-seshubasina (LinkedIn) fromtheheart.co.in (Company)

Top Skills

Entrepreneurship Marketing Strategy Business Strategy

Certifications

Object Detection with Amazon Sagemaker

Use Canva to Create Social Media Marketing Designs

AR 101

Introduction to Augmented Reality and ARCore

Build a Simple App in Android Studio with Java

Honors-Awards

Finalist

Finalist

Finalist

Publications

The 100 perks of Public Speaking

Dileep seshu basina

Helping organisations to create brand awareness.

Greater Hyderabad Area

Summary

A self-starter and quick learner. Versatile skill set with experience in client relations, human resources, graphic designing, web designing, written and oral communication. Recognized skills in mentoring, mediating between employees and in leading team projects. Entrepreneur with strong grit and focus.

Experience

inflooo

Business Development Associate May 2020 - Present (4 months)

Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Codevector Labs - Al solutions Campus Ambassador August 2020 - Present (1 month)

Hyderabad, Telangana, India

Under 25 Space warrior July 2019 - Present (1 year 2 months) Hyderabad Area, India

IEEE

Student Member March 2018 - Present (2 years 6 months)

Hyderabad Area, India

Tinder
Campus Representative
September 2019 - Present (1 year)
Hyderabad Area, India

FROMTHEHEART.CO.IN

Founder and Chief Executive Officer April 2018 - August 2020 (2 years 5 months)

Hyderabad Area, India

Stagger - Everything Creative Human Resources Intern May 2018 - March 2019 (11 months)

Hyderabad, Telangana, India

makethebest.wordpress.com Content Writer January 2016 - February 2017 (1 year 2 months) Hyderabad Area, India

Education

SREYAS INSTITUTE OF ENGINEERING & TECHNOLOGY, TATTIANNARAM

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Electrical, Electronic and Communications Engineering Technology/Technician · (2017 - 2021)

Sri Chaitanya junior kalasala Intermedi, MPC · (2015 - 2017)

Sri vikas model high school

· (2014 - 2015)

sri vagdevi talent school

· (2010 - 2014)